welcome to my presentation and today i
want to talk about what is human
resource management
and specifically how is type
organization of present show
my name is phangdan and you can see my
student id in here
brulen show is the leading reputable
insurance group
in the world with a long history strong
development
a commitment to long-term step and
eviction
investment it presents in vietnam in
1995 and officially put into operation
in 1999
with the message as always listen
already understand
the reason why i choose this firm
because my family member working here
so this makes it easy for me to get the
most accurate
information let's first explore the main
feature of him
as you can see it includes a lot of
function as is stopping
administration pay benefit employee
retention about holding employees and
getting them to stay and not quit early
dealing with employment law and through
regulation on safety and health employee
communication training and development
but according to my results at
prudential there are only
four main functions that are staffing
an essential function that any company
must have to build an organization
development of workplace policy that is
keep
prudential in an effective business
trajectory by setting rules
and compliance with employee training
and development there is a very
important function
to create the development of company the
training of new employees to gradually
get according with the job and develop
them is a
prerequisite for them to gain experience
in bringing
a land number of customers especially
insurance company like prudential
dealing with employment law is
definitely an important function
of our company when hiring people
because
the labor law have employee install
safety in
working process now we look at how hin
function
can help present show we need to look at
objectives
so objective of prudential is increasing
profit
provincial has a lot of branches and
agents so managing them is not easy
for the insurance industry have many
employees so
it's very good because each of them can
market and bring in a long number of
customers to buy insurance for the
company but there is also an industry
with a land number of employees
living after a short time because the
source of customer they bring is limited
and cannot meet the target
that the company offers so the monastery
is very important this gives them more
motivation to work
so that the company can achieve business
score
how do we measure performance in him as
you can see
we can keep track of employee salary
bonus and fire regularly
the cooperation between employee and
matching and manager
can keep check also
whether company can grow or not depend
greatly on hearing from customers
especially its employee it keeps the
company overcome the shortcoming
of employee training
checking the work process in employee in
a department
to know who is good and who is not good
and overcome by insurance stop training
is very important
they are the one who directly seek
client
and persuade them to buy insurance so
professional
is merged the thing to remember from
this presentation
is a normal organization not
organization
are able to fully implement the function
of hrm
every organization should have its own
object to
personal management to achieve the
highest productivity
answering employee benefit to retain
them is really important
anime slides you can see some reference
along with my note
and thank you for listening